philzendia.com 2016-10-04

# Privacy Policy - philZENdia

The privacy of our visitors to our site is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is our privacy policy statement on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit our site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

This website/blog uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when visiting this site. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit Google’s Advertising and Privacy page.

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so at Network Advertising Initiative.

Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it’s Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at Doubleclick as well as opt out options at Google’s Privacy Center

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files via StatCounter and Google Analytics. The information in the log files may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, which pages you visited throughout our site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information..

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

Here is how Google explains cookies: “A ‘cookie’ is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.”

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I suggest my users to be aware of this when they leave this blog and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Advertisers**

We use outside advertising companies to display ads on this website. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and we do not have access to this information. Some of the advertising companies we work with include: Google Adsense and Amazon.com. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns please feel free to [contact us](http://www.philzendia.com/contact).
